让我们快速介绍偏斜对称矩阵。这些矩阵有时被称为
Let’s do a quick introduction to skew symmetric matrices. These matrices are sometimes called
反对称矩阵，它们具有转置的有趣特性
anti-symmetric matrices and they have this interesting property that the transpose is
等于原始矩阵的负数。这些矩阵总是单一的。其
equal to the negative of the original matrix. These matrices are always singular. Their
行列式总是等于零。任何矩阵都是对称矩阵的总和
determinant is always equal to zero. Any matrix is the sum of a symmetric matrix
和一个偏斜对称矩阵。在三维中，我们可以编写偏斜对称矩阵
and a skew symmetric matrix. In three dimensions, we can write the skew symmetric matrix which
以这种方式是三元素向量的函数。所以，我们有一个元素的向量
is a function of a three element vector in this fashion. So, we have a vector whose elements
是X，Y和Z.偏斜对称矩阵看起来像这样。显而易见的特征是
are X, Y, and Z. The skew symmetric matrix looks like this. The obvious features are
零的对角线。那里有两个X.两个Y和两个Z.其中一个有
a diagonal of zeros. There are two X's in there. Two Y's and two Z's. One of them has
一个积极的迹象，其中一个有负号。
a positive sign and one of them has a negative sign.
我们还可以将矢量叉积作为矩阵矢量积。其中一个矩阵
We can also write a vector cross product as a matrix vector product. One of the matrices
是从第一个向量计算的偏斜对称矩阵。
is a skew symmetric matrix computed from the first vector.
这是一个偏斜的对称矩阵，我将与你分享一些经验法则
Here’s a skew symmetric matrix and I am going share with you some rules of thumb for
你如何确定哪些元素是你写这个矩阵的地方。开始
how you work out which elements are where when you write this matrix down. To start
用，有一个零对角线。所以，这很容易。你写了三个零
with, there is a zero diagonal. So, that’s pretty easy. You write three zeros down the
对角线。还有我认为的排除
diagonal. There is also what I think of as an exclusion
规则。因此，在行X和列Y中，该元素将不是额外的Y.它将是另一个
rule. So, in row X and in column Y, that element will not be an extra Y. It will be the other
事情。在这种情况下，它将是Z.如果我们考虑循环旋转序列。
thing. And in this case, it will be a Z. If we consider a cyclic rotation sequence.
所以，我们有一个无穷无尽的序列-X，Y，Z，X，Y，Z等。如果我考虑这个元素
So, we have an endless sequence - X, Y, Z, X, Y, Z and so on. If I consider the element
在Y列和X行中，从Y移动到X，它在循环旋转中向后移动
in column Y and in row X, moving from Y to X, it is going backwards in that cyclic rotation
序列。因为我们正在按顺序倒退，所以我要打一个减号
sequence. Because we are going backwards in the sequence, I am going to put a minus sign
在那个特定的元素上。如果我们在这里看一下这个，我们就要去了
on that particular element. If we look at this one over here, we are going
从Z到X.而且，这是循环旋转序列中的前进。所以，我们给出这个
from Z to X. And, that’s a forward in the cyclic rotation sequence. So, we give this
元素一个积极的迹象。
element a positive sign.